johareez.com 2010-11-23

# Johareez.com :: Privacy Policy

|  |   |  | 

Home | Register | Watch List | My Account | Site Map | Help | Sign In  
  
---  
|  |  |  |  |  | 

_Advanced Search_  
  
---|---  
  
About Us |  Have Products to Sell? |  Customer Service |  Contact Us |  Johareez Explained  
  
|  |  |  Sign In or Register  
---  
|   
---  
|  |     **Jewellery**  
---|---  
|     **New Arrivals**  
|     **FREE Shipping**  
|     **Best Sellers**  
|     **Just Buy It @ Rs.199**  
|     **Gold Jewellery**  
   
|    
---  
|  | 

 **Re.1 No Reserve Auction**  
  
---|---  
| 

**Just Buy It - Fixed Price**  
  
| 

 **Closing Soon - View All**  
  
|   
---  

|    
---  
Privacy Statement for Johareez.com  
**(Effective date: 28 August 2006)**  
Johareez.com is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the site, **www.johareez.com**. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.  
   
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact [privacy@johareez.com](mailto:privacy@johareez.com). If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily address, you should contact TRUSTe at <http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php>. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.  
   
Our goal is to provide you with the best shopping experience possible. Privacy is very important to us. This Privacy Statement will describe the types of information we collect, how we use your information to improve your shopping experience, the limited circumstances under which we might disclose information you provide us and the security efforts we take to safeguard your information.   
   
**What Personal Information About Customers Does Johareez.com Gather?**  
   
**Here are the types of information we gather.**  
   
**Information you give us**  
We receive and store any information you enter on Johareez.com or give us in any other way for our own internal database which is secure and only your payment information is shared with our secure payment gateway provider, Paysignet, through which all online transactions are completed. You provide information to Johareez.com when you register, sign-in, search, purchase products, apply for credit, participate in a contest or questionnaire, sign up for our e-mail newsletters, or communicate with customer service. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone number; gender; e-mail address; or people to whom purchases have been shipped (for example, a gift recipient), including address and phone number.   
   
**More about Cookies**  
   
Johareez.com uses cookies on certain pages to deliver various services and to keep track of your personal preferences. A cookie is small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It functions as your identification card. We also offer certain features that are only available through the use of a cookie. We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. 

If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, most browsers contain a function that allows a user to deny the cookie feature. You can also delete cookie files from your computer at your discretion, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on Johareez.com and you may be required to reenter your password more frequently. Please note that the use of cookies is a necessary part of the Johareez.com technology and is necessary if you wish to access Johareez.com. Disabling the cookie feature on your browser or deleting cookie files from your computer will render you unable to access certain features on Johareez.com. Consequently cookies we serve are tied to the user's information. 

Johareez.com uses cookies to provide its services, to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit different pages on our site, and for other purposes. We do not and will not use cookies to collect private information from you! 

**Information from Other Sources**  
For certain reasons, such as providing you special offers that we think will be of interest, we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily. 

**Our Use of Your Information**  
We use information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on Johareez.com. By visiting our site, you agree that we may use personally identifiable information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize Johareez.com's content, layout, and services. These uses improve Johareez.com and better tailor it to meet your needs. You agree that we may use your information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Johareez.com. 

If you choose to use our referral service ("Email a Friend") to tell a friend about our site and or any product listing, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Johareez.com does store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. 

Your friend may contact us at [support@johareez.com](mailto:support@johareez.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.   

**Does Johareez.com Disclose the Information It Receives?**  
   
As a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. However, the following describes some of the ways that your personally identifiable information may be disclosed. 

**Business Partners and Selected Vendors We Do Not Control**  
We work closely with certain business partners and carefully selected vendors to provide you with access to their product offerings or to their online stores (for example, the Partners listed on Johareez.com and Johareez products available at Johareez.com). We may share our data, including personally identifiable information about you, with these business partners or selected vendors, and they may use this information to offer you products and/or services that may be of interest to you. If you choose to access the Partners, disclose information to the Partners, place orders from the Partners, and/or grant them permission to collect information about you, then their use of your information is governed by their applicable privacy policies. To prevent our disclosure of your personally identifiable information to one of these third parties, you can choose not use their services or order their products. Because we do not control the privacy practices of these third parties, you should evaluate their practices before deciding to use their services or place orders with them for their products. 

**Agents**  
We use an outside shipping company to fulfill orders, and a credit card processing company (Paysignet E-Transactions) to complete payments for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes. 

**Service Providers**  
Johareez.com uses a third-party tracking service called Omniture SiteCatalyst that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our Site in aggregate form. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

**Business Transfers**  
As we continue to develop our business, we might buy the online and/or off-line retail operations of others. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that Johareez.com or substantially all of its assets are acquired by or transferred to another entity, customer information would likely be one of the transferred assets. 

**Government and Legal Disclosures of Your Information**  
We may disclose information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we believe necessary in connection with an investigation of illegal activity that may expose you or us to legal liability. In addition, if you have purchased products from us on extended payment terms, it may be necessary for us to file certain information about you with state or local government offices to perfect our security interest in the products so purchased, or to provide certain information about you to collection agencies in the event of non-payment or a payment dispute. 

**Links to and from Other Web Sites**  
Johareez.com regularly offers links to other Web sites, which may include the Partner Web sites of our business partners or selected vendors. These Web sites have their own policies regarding privacy. In addition, you may have linked to Johareez.com through another site, such as by means of a banner advertisement for Johareez.com on that other site. In such cases, the site you linked from may collect information from people who click on the banner or link. You may want to refer to the privacy policies on those sites to see how they collect and use this information.   

**What Choices Do You Have?**  
   
You can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of other Johareez.com features. Johareez.com offers the ability to correct or change the information collected through your use of Johareez.com. Instructions are listed in " My Account" area under "Account Details." You can change this information at any time and as often as necessary. If you experience problems or have any questions about our services, contact us. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records. 

**Electronic Newsletters and E-Mails**   
Johareez.com offers free electronic newsletters as a service to our users. In addition, Johareez.com may periodically send you information and product promotions via e-mail. You may cancel your subscription to our electronic newsletter or end product related e-mails from Johareez.com at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of every such newsletter or e-mail. You may also elect to remove your e-mail address from our newsletter and e-mail mailing lists by sending us an email. 

**Security**   
Johareez.com uses industry standard practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, including "firewalls" and Secure Socket Layers (SSL). Johareez.com treats data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside the company. 

**Children**  
Children are not eligible to use Johareez.com and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you can use Johareez.com only in conjunction with your parents or guardians 

**Terms of Use, Notices, and Revisions**   
If you choose to visit Johareez.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Statement and our Terms of Use policy. If you have any concern about privacy at Johareez.com, please send us a thorough description of your concern. Our business changes constantly. This Privacy Statement will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Statement in effect at the time of use. Johareez.com reserves the right to change or update the policy at any time by placing a prominent notice on our site, shall be effective immediately upon posting on this site. 

Johareez.com secure checkout system is powered by Paysignet E-Transactions Pvt. Ltd. ([www.paysignet.com](http://www.paysignet.com/)). In the process of completing checkout on Johareez.com, all the order information such as the order details, contact and shipping information is stored on Johareez.com’s servers. Only after customer places his or her order by clicking on "Place Order" button on the site, then only is the order detail information redirected to the Paysignet secure payment site, www.paysignet.com, where then the customer is provided payment options to choose from to complete his or her payment for the order. The paysignet payment site page is customized by Johareez.com to give the look and feel of the site. All the payment details collected on the payment site page is then collected and stored by Paysignet.com to authorize payments for Johareez.com. Once the payment authorization process has been completed, the customer is redirected back to Johareez.com with a payment confirmation notification. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please email us at [support@johareez.com](mailto:support@johareez.com) or contact us at:  

**Johareez.com Auctions Pvt. Ltd.**  
S-10, Jeevan Vihar  
New Colony, Jaipur 302001  
RAJASTHAN (INDIA)  
Phone: (91-141) 3253500   
  
* * *  
  
| 

|   | 

|  Get special offers and discounts -- Sign up for email |  |   
  
---|---|---  
  
|  |   | **Johareez.com**  
About Us  
Register / Login  
Contact Us  
Customer Service  
Jobs  
In the News | **For Sellers**  
Have Products to Sell?  
Promote Your Auctions  
Sellers Help | **For Buyers**  
Pay  
Track Your Order  
Spread the Word   
Newsletter Archives  
Customer Review | **Need to Know**  
Shipping Guarantee  
Announcements  
Terms of Service  
Privacy Statement  
FAQ's  
---|---|---|---|---  
  
|  |  | * ISO 9001:2008 Registered Company  
* Secure Shopping Guaranteed  
---  
  
Use of this website constitutes acceptance of the Johareez.com [User Agreement](http://www.johareez.com/pdf/johareez_user_agreement.pdf) and Privacy Statement. Designated trademarks, logos and brands are the property of their respective owners. Copyright © 2010  
Johareez.com Auctions Pvt. Ltd.  
All Rights Reserved.   
  
|        
---  
Credit Cards | Net-Banking | Cash-on-Delivery (COD)  
| [](http://www.facebook.com/johareez) | [Find us on  
Facebook](http://www.facebook.com/johareez)  
---|---  
[](http://blog.johareez.com/) | [Blog  
Johareez](http://blog.johareez.com/)  
|  Official Johareez.com Time: Wednesday, 24 November 2010 04:05:24 IST  |   |   
---|---|---
